ensogo.com.ph 2011-12-28

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy   
---  
|   
---  
|  Introduction  
---  
Ensogo Inc, (herein after referred as Ensogo) including subsidiaries and affiliates provide you, its Services (herein after referred as “Website”) adhere to the Privacy Policy describe herein.  
Thank you for visiting our Website (Ensogo.com.ph). This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this Website. Please read this privacy policy before using the Website or submitting any personal information. By using the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the Website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.  
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this Website only. If you link to other Websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.  
   
Collection of Information  
Ensogo collects personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.  
   
Tracking (Cookie) Technology  
The Website may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Website, and understanding how visitors use the Website. Cookies can also help customize the Website for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. However, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. An aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.  
   
Distribution of Information  
Ensogo may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.  
   
Commitment to Data Security  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) will have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt-out of further mailings.  
   
Privacy Contact Information  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:  
   
**Ensogo Inc.**  
2nd Floor W High Street Building, 28th St., Cor. 11th Ave.,  
Bonifacio Global City, Taguig, Philippines 1634  
**Phone:** (+63) 2-555-6868   
**Fax:** +632-555-6810  
   
Ensogo reserves the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted on the Website.
